golftournamentregistry.com 2006-06-17

# Golf Tournament Registry: Online Golf Tournament Registry. Find & Advertise Golf Tournaments

**GolfTournamentRegistry.com Privacy Policy**

Revised August 1, 2005

In addition to reviewing this privacy policy, please read our User Agreement. Your use of GolfTournamentRegistry.com constitutes agreement to the User Agreement terms and conditions.

This Privacy Policy may be modified from time to time; the date of the most recent revisions will appear on this page, so check back often. Continued access of GolfTournamentRegistry.com by you will constitute your acceptance of any changes or revisions to the Privacy Policy.

It is the goal of GolfTournamentRegistry.com to bring you information that is tailored to your individual needs and, at the same time, protect your privacy. The following is a summary of the various ways we treat the information you provide us while using our site.

**THE TYPE OF INFORMATION GolfTournamentRegistry.com COLLECTS**

GolfTournamentRegistry.com generally collects personally identifying information with your specific knowledge and consent. For instance when you subscribe to our services you are asked to provide information such as your e-mail address, name or phone number.

**HOW GolfTournamentRegistry.com USES INFORMATION PROVIDED BY YOU**

GolfTournamentRegistry.com uses this information to provide you with the service you have requested. We may also use the information to communicate with you about new features, products or services, or to improve the services that we offer by tailoring them to your needs.

GolfTournamentRegistry.com does not sell any of our users' personal information. If you've registered on any part of GolfTournamentRegistry.com, you may also change or update your member preferences or information within any section of the site where you have signed up, registered or created any type of account.

We also allow access to our database by third parties that provide us with services, such as technical maintenance, but only for the purpose of and to the extent necessary to provide those services. And if you choose to purchase items through features on our site, we may forward your information to third parties for services such as credit card processing and order fulfillment. We may also provide your information to our advertisers, so that they can serve ads to you that meet your needs or match your interests. While GolfTournamentRegistry.com will seek to require such third parties to follow appropriate privacy policies and will not authorize them to use this information except for the express purpose for which it is provided, GolfTournamentRegistry.com does not bear any responsibility for any actions or policies of third parties. There may also be occasion when we are legally required to provide access to our database in order to cooperate with police investigations or other legal proceedings. In those instances, the information is provided only for that purpose.

**COOKIES**

You may have heard about "cookies," information that is placed by a Website in a storage place on your own computer. We use cookies to control the display of ads, to track usage patterns on the site, to deliver content, and to record registration and personalization information. For example, if you register on any part of GolfTournamentRegistry.com, you can opt to save your user name and password on your computer. We can provide this convenience by placing a cookie on your computer.

Our cookies may contain personally identifiable information.

Some of our advertisers occasionally serve you cookies as well. We do not have control over cookies placed by advertisers.

If you don't want cookies, your Web browser likely includes an option that allows you to not accept them. However, if you set your browser to refuse cookies, some portions of GolfTournamentRegistry.com may not function properly.

While your individual information is protected as outlined above, we reserve the right to use aggregated, anonymous data about our users as a group for any business purpose, such as analyzing usage trends and seeking compatible advertisers and partners.

**IP ADDRESS**

Your Internet Protocol ("IP") address is usually associated with the place from which you enter the Internet, like your Internet Service Provider, your company or your university. We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, gather broad demographic information, and administer our website.

**KIDS AND PARENTS**

GolfTournamentRegistry.com is not intended for use by children, especially those under age 13. No one under age 13 is allowed to provide any personal information or use our public areas. Minors between the ages of 13 and 17 must get the permission of their parent(s) or legal guardian(s) before making purchases, including subscriptions, on this site.

If your children disclose information about themselves in our public areas, they may get unsolicited messages from other parties. Accordingly, you should tell them not to do so.

If you have other concerns or questions about any aspect of this policy, you may e-mail us .
